Finding Aid for Harlan Henthorne Hatcher Papers
Bentley Historical Library
- University of Michigan Presidency
  - Yearly Correspondence File
    - 1962-1963
      - Ma-Mz (Box 34)
        (34-20)
      - Michigan (Box 34)
        (34-21)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 34)
      - Michigan Audit Commission (Box 34)
      - M.U.R.A. (Box 34)
        (34-22)
      - Music School (Box 34)
      - Michigan Week, 1963 (Box 34)
        (34-23)
      - Michigan Week, 1963 (Box 34)
        (34-24)
      - Na-Nz (Box 34)
        (34-25)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 34)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 35)
        (35-1)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 35)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 35)
        (35-2)
      - Peace Corps (Box 35)
        (35-3)
      - Public Instruction. Department of Public Instruction (Box 35)
      - Q (Box 35)
        (35-4)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 35)
      - Russel Award (Box 35)
        (35-5)
      - Sa-Sz (Box 35)
        (35-6)
      - Schnitzer (Robert) (Box 35)
        (35-7)
      - Senate Advisory Committee (Box 35)
      - Speakers (Box 35)
      - T-U (Box 35)
        (35-8)
      - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 35)
        (35-9)
      - United States Government (Box 35)
      - Va-Vz (Box 35)
        (35-10)
      - Vetulonian (Etruscan Foundation) (Box 35)
      - Visitors (Box 35)
        (35-11)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 35)
        (35-12)
      - Water Pollution Lab (Box 35)
        (35-13)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 35)
    - 1963-1964
      - Aa-Az (Box 35)
        (35-14)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 35)
        (35-15)
      - American (Box 35)
      - American Council on Education (Box 35)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 35)
        (35-16)
      - Association of American Colleges (Box 35)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 35)
        (35-17)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 35)
        (35-18)
      - Bledsoe (Box 35)
        (35-19)
      - Branch Colleges (Box 35)
      - Ca-Cz (Box 35)
        (35-20)
      - Community Colleges (Box 35)
        (35-21)
      - Condolence Letters (Box 35)
      - Council of Ten (Box 35)
        (35-22)
      - Council on Financial Aid (Box 35)
      - Da-Dz (Box 35)
        (35-23)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 35)
        (35-24)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 36)
        (36-1)
      - Fellowships, etc. (Box 36)
        (36-2)
      - Fellowships, etc. (A-M) (Box 36)
        (36-3)
      - Fellowships, etc. (N-Z) (Box 36)
        (36-4)
      - Flint College (Box 36)
        (36-5)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 36)
        (36-6)
      - Ha-Hh (Box 36)
        (36-7)
      - Hi-Hz (Box 36)
        (36-8)
      - Higgins (Box 36)
      - I (Box 36)
        (36-9)
      - Introduction Letters (Box 36)
      - J-K (Box 36)
        (36-10)
      - Kennedy (John F.) (Box 36)
        (36-11)
      - Johnson (Lyndon B.) (Box 36)
      - La-Lz (Box 36)
        (36-12)
      - Lewis (Box 36)
      - Likert (Rensis) (Box 36)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 36)
        (36-13)
      - Michigan (Box 36)
        (36-14)
      - Michigan Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 36)
      - Michigan College Presidents (Box 36)
        (36-15)
      - Michigan Department of Economic Expansion (Box 36)
      - Michigan Legislative Service Bureau (Box 36)
      - Michigan Union and League (Box 36)
      - Michigan State University (Box 36)
      - Michigan Week (Box 36)
        (36-16)
      - Michigan Week (Box 36)
        (36-17)
      - Michigan Week (Box 36)
        (36-18)
      - M.U.R.A. (Box 36)
        (36-19)
      - Mott (Charles S.) (Box 36)
      - Murphy (Irene) (Box 36)
      - Na-Nz (Box 36)
        (36-20)
      - National (Box 36)
        (36-21)
      - N.A.S.A. (Box 37)
        (37-1)
      - National Medal of Science (Box 37)
        (37-2)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 37)
      - North Central Association (Box 37)
      - N.R.O.T.C. (Box 37)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 37)
        (37-3)
      - Olson (Box 37)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 37)
        (37-4)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 37)
        (37-5)
      - Peace Corps (Box 37)
        (37-6)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 37)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 37)
      - Presidents Club (Box 37)
        (37-7)
      - Q (Box 37)
        (37-8)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 37)
      - Radock (Michael) (Box 37)
      - Rankin (Box 37)
        (37-9)
      - Regents (Box 37)
      - Registration (Box 37)
      - Research (Box 37)
      - Romney (George) (Box 37)
        (37-10)
      - R.O.T.C. (Box 37)
        (37-11)
      - Russel Award (Box 37)
      - Russian Visitors (Box 37)
      - Sa-Sn (Box 37)
        (37-12)
      - So-Sz (Box 37)
        (37-13)
      - Sawyer (Ralph) (Box 37)
        (37-14)
      - Schnitzer (Robert) (Box 37)
        (37-15)
      - Senate Advisory (Box 37)
        (37-16)
      - Sorenson (Box 37)
      - Sororities and Fraternities (Box 37)
        (37-17)
      - Speakers (Box 37)
        (37-18)
      - Statistical Service (Box 37)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 37)
      - Student Organizations (Box 37)
        (37-19)
      - Student Symposium (Box 37)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 38)
        (38-1)
      - Thurber (Donald) (Box 38)
      - U (Box 38)
        (38-2)
      - United States Government (Box 38)
        (38-3)
      - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 38)
        (38-4)
      - Va-Vz (Box 38)
        (38-5)
      - Van Zyl (Box 38)
      - Venezuelan Students (Box 38)
      - Voice of America (Box 38)
      - Visitors (Box 38)
        (38-6)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 38)
        (38-7)
      - Williams (R.L.) (Box 38)
        (38-8)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 38)
        (38-9)
    - 1964-1965
      - Aa-Az (Box 38)
        (38-10)
      - Accrediting (Box 38)
        (38-11)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 38)
      - A.E.R.O. (Box 38)
        (38-12)
      - Alumni Association (Box 38)
      - American (Box 38)
        (38-13)
      - American Council on Education (Box 38)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 38)
        (38-14)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 38)
      - Associated Midwestern Universities (Box 38)
        (38-15)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 38)
        (38-16)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 38)
        (38-17)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 38)
        (38-18)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 39)
        (39-1)
      - Co-Cz (Box 39)
        (39-2)
      - Commendation Letters (Box 39)
        (39-3)
      - Community Colleges (Box 39)
      - Condolence Letters (Box 39)
      - Continuing Education for Women (Box 39)
        (39-4)
      - Co-op Program (Box 39)
      - Council of Ten (Box 39)
      - Council for Financial Aid to Education (Box 39)
        (39-5)
      - Da-Dz (Box 39)
        (39-6)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 39)
        (39-7)
      - Economics Club of Detroit (Box 39)
        (39-8)
      - Economic Education (Box 39)
      - Economic Opportunity Program (Box 39)
      - Engineering Convocation (Box 39)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 39)
        (39-9)
      - Faculty Promotions (Box 39)
      - Fellowships, etc. (Box 39)
        (39-10)
      - Fellowships, etc. (A-M) (Box 39)
        (39-11)
      - Fellowships, etc. (N-Z) (Box 39)
        (39-12)
      - Flint College (Box 39)
        (39-13)
      - Football (Box 39)
        (39-14)
      - Ford Motor Company (Box 39)
      - Ford Foundation (Box 39)
      - Foreign Students (Box 39)
      - Forsyth (Box 39)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 39)
        (39-15)
      - Governing Boards (Box 39)
      - Graduate School (Box 39)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 39)
        (39-16)
      - Hatcher Professorships (Box 39)
        (39-17)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 39)
      - Hinsdale Report (Box 39)
        (39-18)
      - Housing (Box 39)
      - I (Box 40)
        (40-1)
      - Introduction Letters (Box 40)
      - J (Box 40)
        (40-2)
      - Johnson (Lyndon B.) (Box 40)
      - Ka-Kz (Box 40)
        (40-3)
      - La-Lz (Box 40)
        (40-4)
      - Law School (Box 40)
        (40-5)
      - L.S.&A. (Box 40)
      - Ma-Mc (Box 40)
        (40-6)
      - Md-Mz (Box 40)
        (40-7)
      - Michigan (Box 40)
        (40-8)
      - Michigan Coordinating Council for Higher Education (Box 40)
        (40-9)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 40)
        (40-10)
      - Michigan Legislature (Box 40)
        (40-11)
      - M.U.R.A. (Box 40)
      - Music School (Box 40)
      - Na-Nz (Box 40)
        (40-12)
      - National (Box 40)
      - N.A.S.A. (Box 40)
      - O (Marina Oswald) (Box 40)
        (40-13)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 40)
      - Pa-Pn (Box 40)
        (40-14)
      - Po-Pz (Box 40)
        (40-15)
      - Q-R (Box 40)
        (40-16)
      - Romney (George) (Box 40)
      - Sa-Sz (Box 40)
        (40-17)
      - Sackett (Ray) (Box 40)
        (40-18)
      - Sink (Charles) (Box 40)
      - Speakers (Box 40)
      - Sororities and Fraternities (Box 40)
        (40-19)
      - Stirton (W.E.) (Box 40)
      - Student Affairs (Box 40)
        (40-20)
      - Student Organizations (Box 40)
      - T-U (Box 41)
        (41-1)
      - United States Government (Box 41)
      - U.S. Congress (Box 41)
      - Va-Vz (Box 41)
        (41-2)
      - Vietnam Protest (Box 41)
      - Visitors (Box 41)
      - Wa-Wz (Box 41)
        (41-3)
      - White House Conference (Box 41)
      - X-Y-Z (Box 41)
    - 1965-1966
      - Aa-Az (Box 41)
        (41-4)
      - Accrediting (Box 41)
        (41-5)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 41)
      - Agency for International Development (Box 41)
        (41-6)
      - American (Box 41)
        (41-7)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 41)
        (41-8)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 41)
        (41-9)
      - Association of American Universities (Meetings) (Box 41)
        (41-10)
      - Athletics (Box 41)
        (41-11)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 41)
        (41-12)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 41)
        (41-13)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 41)
        (41-14)
      - Co-Cz (Box 41)
        (41-15)
      - California. University of California (Box 41)
        (41-16)
      - Clements Library (Box 41)
      - Commendation and Condolence Letters (Box 41)
        (41-17)
      - Continuing Education For Women (Box 41)
      - C.F.A.E. (Box 41)
        (41-18)
      - Council of Ten (Box 41)
        (41-19)
      - Cudlip (William B.) (Box 41)
      - Da-Dz (Box 42)
        (42-1)
      - Dearborn Campus (Box 42)
      - Ea-Ez (Box 42)
        (42-2)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 42)
        (42-3)
      - Fellowships, etc. (Box 42)
        (42-4)
      - Fellowships, etc (A-N) (Box 42)
        (42-5)
      - Fellowships, etc. (O-Z) (Box 42)
        (42-6)
      - Flint College (Box 42)
        (42-7)
      - Football (Box 42)
      - Ford (Box 42)
      - Foreign Students (Box 42)
      - Fries (Box 42)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 42)
        (42-8)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 42)
        (42-9)
      - Heyns (Roger) (Box 42)
        (42-10)
      - Highway Research (Box 42)
      - Hoey (Box 42)
      - I (Box 42)
        (42-11)
      - Introduction Letters (Box 42)
      - J-K (Box 42)
        (42-12)
      - La-Lz (Box 42)
        (42-13)
      - L.S.& A. (Box 42)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 42)
        (42-14)
      - Medical School (Box 42)
        (42-15)
      - Mental Retardation (Box 42)
      - Michigan (Box 42)
        (42-16)
      - Michigan Association of Colleges and Universities (Box 42)
        (42-17)
      - Michigan Senators and Republicans (Box 42)
      - Mott (Charles S.) (Box 42)
      - Murphy (Irene) (Box 42)
      - M.U.R.A. (Box 42)
      - Michigan State University (Box 43)
        (43-1)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 43)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 43)
      - Na-Nz (Box 43)
        (43-2)
      - National (Box 43)
        (43-3)
      - N.A.S.A. (Box 43)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 43)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 43)
        (43-4)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 43)
      - Pa-Pz (Box 43)
        (43-5)
      - Pierpont (W.K.) (Box 43)
        (43-6)
      - Positions, Applications for (Box 43)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 43)
        (Controversy and Resignation)
        (43-7)
      - Power (Eugene) (Box 43)
        (43-8)
      - President (Box 43)
        (Selection Policy)
      - Q-R (Box 43)
        (43-9)
      - Regents (Box 43)
      - Romney (George) (Box 43)
        (43-10)
      - Residential College (Box 43)
        (43-11)
      - Sa-Sn (Box 43)
        (43-12)
      - So-Sz (Box 43)
        (43-13)
      - Scholarships, etc. (Box 43)
        (43-14)
      - Smith (Allan) (Box 43)
        (43-15)
      - Sororities and Fraternities (Box 43)
      - Speakers (Box 43)
      - Student Organizations (Box 43)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 43)
      - Technical Services Council (Box 43)
        (43-16)
      - Theatre (Box 43)
      - Va-Vz (Box 44)
        (44-1)
      - U. S. Congress (Box 44)
        (44-2)
      - U.S. Government (Box 44)
      - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 44)
      - University Budget and Research Association (Box 44)
        (44-3)
      - Va-Vz (Box 44)
        (44-4)
      - Visitors (Box 44)
      - Vietnam (Box 44)
        (44-5)
      - W-Z (Box 44)
        (44-6)
    - 1966-1967
      - Aa-Az (Box 44)
        (44-7)
      - Accrediting (Box 44)
        (44-8)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 44)
      - Act 124 (Box 44)
      - A.I.D. Committee on A.I.D. (Box 44)
        (44-9)
      - American (Box 44)
      - American Council on Education (Box 44)
        (44-10)
      - Anonymous-Asylum (Box 44)
      - Applications for Positions (Box 44)
        (44-11)
      - Argonne Universities Association (Box 44)
      - Arms Control (Box 44)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 44)
        (44-12)
      - Athletics (Box 44)
        (44-13)
      - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 44)
      - Ba-Bn (Box 44)
        (44-14)
      - Bo-Bz (Box 44)
        (44-15)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 45)
        (45-1)
      - Co-Cz (Box 45)
        (45-2)
      - Carpenter (Box 45)
        (45-3)
      - Cinema Guild (Box 45)
      - Commendation and Condolence Letters (Box 45)
        (45-4)
      - Council of Ten (Box 45)
      - Cutler (Richard Loyd) (Box 45)
      - Da-Dz (Box 45)
        (45-5)
      - Draft Problems (Box 45)
        (45-6)
      - E (Box 45)
        (45-7)
      - Fa-Fz (Box 45)
        (45-8)
      - Fair Lane (Box 45)
        (45-9)
      - Ga-Gz (Box 45)
        (45-10)
      - Ha-Hz (Box 45)
        (45-11)
      - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 45)
        (45-12)
      - I (Box 45)
        (45-13)
      - Invitations, Ann Arbor (Box 45)
      - J-K (Box 45)
        (45-14)
      - La-Lz (Box 45)
        (45-15)
      - Ma-Mz (Box 45)
        (45-16)
      - Michigan (Box 45)
        (45-17)
      - Michigan Congressmen and Senators (Box 45)
      - Michigan Council of State College Presidents (Box 46)
        (46-1)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 46)
        (46-2)
      - Michigan Legislature (Box 46)
      - Michigan Department of Education (Box 46)
        (46-3)
      - M.U.R.A. (Box 46)
        (46-4)
      - Murphy Papers (Box 46)
      - Na-Nz (Box 46)
        (46-5)
      - National. (Box 46)
        (46-6)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 46)
        (46-7)
      - Outstanding Achievement Awards (Box 46)
        (46-8)
      - P (Box 46)
        (46-9)
      - Q (Box 46)
        (46-10)
      - Ra-Rz (Box 46)
      - Romney (George) (Box 46)
        (46-11)
      - Sa-Sn (Box 46)
        (46-12)
      - So-Sz (Box 46)
        (46-13)
      - Social Revolution (Box 46)
      - T (Box 46)
        (46-14)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 46)
        (46-15)
      - Va-Vz (Box 46)
        (46-16)
      - Visitors (Box 46)
      - W-X-Y-Z (Box 46)
        (46-17)
    - 1967
      - Aa-Az (Box 47)
        (47-1)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 47)
        (47-2)
      - American (Box 47)
      - American Council on Education (Box 47)
        (47-3)
      - Association of American Universities (Box 47)
      - Ba-Bz (Box 47)
        (47-4)
      - Bentley (Alvin M.) (Box 47)
      - Ca-Cn (Box 47)
        (47-5)
      - Co-Cz (Box 47)
        (47-6)
      - Da-Dz (Box 47)
        (47-7)
      - E (Box 47)
        (47-8)
      - F (Box 47)
        (47-9)
      - G (Box 47)
        (47-10)
      - H-I-J (Box 47)
        (47-11)
      - K (Box 47)
        (47-12)
      - L (Box 47)
        (47-13)
      - M (Box 47)
        (47-14)
      - Na-Nz (Box 47)
        (47-15)
      - National (Box 47)
        (47-16)
      - National Association of State Universities (Box 47)
      - National Science Foundation (Box 47)
      - Oa-Oz (Box 47)
        (47-17)
      - Orientals Congress (Box 47)
      - P (Box 47)
        (47-18)
      - Q-R (Box 47)
        (47-19)
      - Sa-Sz (Box 47)
        (47-20)
      - Schnitzer (Robert) (Box 47)
        (47-21)
      - Senate Advisory (Box 47)
      - Smith (Allan) (Box 47)
      - Student Organizations (Box 47)
      - Ta-Tz (Box 47)
        (47-22)
      - Ua-Uz (Box 47)
        (47-23)
      - United States Government (Box 47)
        (47-24)
      - U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 47)
      - University Research Association (Box 47)
      - Va-Vz (Box 48)
        (48-1)
      - Visitors (Box 48)
      - W-Z (Box 48)
        (48-2)
  - Organizational Responsibilities/Special Activities as President
    The Organizational Responsibilities/Special Activities as President series (6.3 linear ft.; 1953-1967) is the title given to those categories of files, kept separate by the president's office from the Yearly Correspondence Files and covering an extended period of time. These files cover Hatcher's participation as representative of the University of Michigan with different academic and professional organizations. These include the Michigan Council of State College Presidents, the Midwestern University Research Association, the Commission on the Education of Women of the American Council on Education, the Institute for Defense Analyses, the Citizens Committee on Higher Education, the Council for Financial Aid to Education, the Joint Office of Institutional Research, and the National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges. In addition, this series includes files relating to the celebration of the university's sesquicentennial, both ceremonial observances and lectures and fund-raising opportunities. Lastly, within this series are those letters and other working materials accumulated in response to the changing of the name of Michigan State College to Michigan State University in 1955.
    - Michigan Council of State College Presidents, 1958-1964
      - Agenda, 1959 (Box 48)
      - Academic Administration Committee, 1959 (Box 48)
      - Applications for Co-ordinator Position, 1960-1961 (Box 48)
      - Correspondence (Box 48)
      - Co-ordinator for Higher Education (Box 48)
      - Joint Superintendent-College-University Relations Committee (Box 48)
      - Meetings, January 9, 1961; March 13, 1961; November 10, 1961; 3 folders (Box 48)
      - Michigan Co-ordinating Council for Public Higher Education
        - 1961-1962 (Box 48)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 48)
        - 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box 48)
      - Michigan Co-ordinating Council of State College Field Services (Box 48)
      - Michigan School Finance and Education Program (Box 48)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 48)
      - Minutes
        - 1958-1961 (Box 48)
        - 1960-1961 (Box 48)
        - 1961-1962 (Box 48)
        - 1962-1963 (Box 48)
        - 1963-1964 (Box 49)
      - Office of Information and Research (Box 49)
      - Statements from Member Institutions (Box 49)
    - Midwestern University Research Association, 1954-1962
      - Minutes, 1954-1962 (Box 49)
      - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 49)
      - Proposal to Atomic Energy Commission (Box 49)
      - Organization (Box 49)
      - Correspondence (Box 49)
      - Meetings-Expenses (Box 50)
      - Reports, Miscellanea (Box 50)
      - Site Selection Committee Reports (Box 50)
    - Sesquicentennial Celebration of the University of Michigan
      - Major Ceremony I, March 1967 (Box 50)
      - Major Ceremony II, March 1967 (Box 50)
      - Major Ceremony III, March 1967 (Box 50)
      - Major Ceremony IV, "Voices of Civilization" (Box 50)
      - Major Ceremony V, "Fertility and Family Planning" (Box 50)
      - H.W. Hildebrant's File (University Secretary) (Box 50)
      - H.W. Hildebrant's File (University Secretary) (Box 51)
      - Sesquicentennial, 1967 (Box 51)
        (General)
      - Sesquicentennial Capital Funds (Box 51)
      - Sesquicentennial Citizens Committee (Box 51)
      - Sesquicentennial Fund Raising (Box 51)
      - Sesquicentennial Capital Funds (Box 51)
      - Chrysler Corporation (Box 51)
      - Bentley, Alvin (Box 51)
      - Fifty-five Million Dollar Fund (Box 51)
      - Personal Letters (Box 51)
      - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 51)
      - General Motors Corporation (Box 51)
      - Invitations (Box 51)
      - Hatcher Speeches (Box 51)
      - Hatcher's Personal Visits with Special Individuals and Corporations (Box 51)
      - Congressional Day (Box 51)
      - Fund Raising (Box 51)
      - General Correspondence (Box 51)
      - Fifty-five Million Dollar Campaign-Final Report (Box 51)
    - Commission on the Education of Women
      (American Council on Education)
      - January 1953-June 1953 (Box 51)
      - July 1953-January 1954 (Box 51)
      - January 1954-June 1954 (Box 51)
      - July 1954-June 1955, June 1957; March 1960 (Box 51)
    - Institute for Defense Analyses
      - 1958-1967, 8 folders (Box 52)
    - Association of American Universities
      - Correspondence, May 1963-February 1964 (Box 52)
      - Correspondence, March 1964-July 1964 (Box 52)
      - Meeting-New York City, October 27-28, 1964 (Box 52)
      - Spring Meeting, Washington, D.C, April 20-21, 1965 (Box 52)
    - Citizens Committee on Higher Education
      - Governor Romney's "Blue Ribbon Committee, January 1963-May 1964 (Box 52)
      - Report of Citizens Committee on Higher Education in Michigan, March 1965 (Box 52)
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education
      - Correspondence, May 1955-June 1958 (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, July 1958-June 1959 (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, July 1959-June 1960 (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, July 1960-December 1960 (Box 53)
      - Correspondence, August 1961-July 1962 (Box 53)
      - Minutes, December 1954-June 1957 (Box 53)
      - Minutes, July 1957-June 1960 (Box 53)
      - Minutes, September 1960-January 1963 (Box 53)
      - Memorandum, July 1962-March 1963 (Box 53)
      - Agenda, March 1959-March 1963 (Box 53)
    - Joint Office of Institutional Research
      - Miscellaneous, 1957-1967 (Box 53)
    - Michigan State University (Change of Name)
      - Working material, President Hannah letter, and Miscellaneous (Box 53)
      - Letters from Dean E. Blythe Stason, University of Michigan Law School (Box 53)
      - Opinion of Attorney General Frank G. Millard, March 31, 1954 (Box 53)
      - Clippings, etc (Box 53)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
      - Letters Against Name Change (alumni and others) (Box 53)
      - Letters criticizing University of Michigan, March 1955; April 1955 (Box 53)
      - Replies-State Officers, Senators, Representatives, Presidents (Box 53)
      - Letters Sent to Senators and Representatives by Alumni, etc (Box 53)
      - Letter Sent to House of Representatives, February 28, 1955 (Box 53)
      - Letter Sent to Senate and House of Representatives, March 19, 1955 (Box 53)
      - Letter Sent to Senate, and others, circa March 3 1955 (Box 53)
    - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges
      (name changed in 1964 from Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges)
      - General, 1962-1964; 6 folders (Box 53)
      - General, 1964-1967; 3 folders (Box 54)
  - Ceremonial/Public Role as President